They were startled and frightened , thinking they saw a ghost .
He said to them ,
" Why are you troubled , and why do doubts rise in your minds ?
Look at my hands and my feet . It is I myself ! Touch me and see ;
a ghost does not have flesh and bones , as you see I have . "
Luke 24 : 37-39
Presented by 20th Century Fox4
Distribution by 20th Century Fox Korea Corporation and Well Go USA Entertainment
Production Company Side Mirror
Fox International Productions ( Korea )
Kwak Do-Won
Hwang Jung-Min
It 's still dawn . What is it ?
Somebody died .
Chun Woo-Hee
Who ?
You know Cho , the ginseng grower ?
Yeah .
His wife died .
It 's pouring out there ...
Produced by Suh Dong Hyun and Kim Ho Sung Production Investment by Paul Huh Sung II
Hey , where are you off to ?
Somebody died .
Who ?
Wife of the ginseng farmer .
Executive Producers : Robert Friedland and John Penotti
That 's all I know .
But she 's so young .
You said it .
- Don 't go without eating . - I gotta hurry .
Just a bite !
Hurrying won 't bring back the dead .
Director of Photography Hong Kyung Pyo
But I need to go now .
Eat , will you ?
Come on .
Gaffer : Kim Chang Ho Production Designer : Lee Hwo Kyung
What happened ?
Not sure .
- Production Sound Mixer : Kim Sin Yong ( K.P.A. ) - I think someone killed her .
Action Choreographers : Yoo Sang Seob , Kwon Gui Duck
What kind of fucker Kills people ?
Damned son of a bitch .
Costume Designer : Chae Kyung Hwa Makeup Hair Artist : Kim Seo Young
Someone died ?
Eat up , dear .
Who died ?
Special Effects by Kim Kwang Soo ( Extreme FX )
Special Makeup by Hwang Hyo Kyun , Kwak Tae Yong ( Cell )
Eat your breakfast .
Bye , dad .
Editor : Kim Sun Min
Music Composers : Jang Young Gyu and Dalpalan Sound Supervisor : Park Yong Ki ( Studio K )
VFX Supervisor : Cheong Jai Hoon
Digital Intermediate Supervisor : Kevin Kang ( DEXTER , THE EYE )
What took so long ? !
Gimme a raincoat .
Hurry up !
We 've got two corpses here .
Where 's the Captain ?
He went to Seoul , remember ?
Right .
Come on !
I 'm coming .
Line Producer : Lim Min Sub
Written and Directed by Na Hong Jin
Look at me , Heung-guk !
Let go of me !
I 'm his uncle !
Jong-gu !
Heung-guk , how could you do this ?
Sergeant .
Did it with this , I guess . Stabbed him , like , 20 times ?
Holy shit .
What 's that ?
Looks like the body was moved here after the murder .
What a mess .
That 's Cho - the husband ?
Looks that way .
I 'll be damned .
And the kid ?
We took him to a relative
Why 'd he do it ?
I don 't smell booze on him , but he 's not talking .
Could be high on something . How else could he end up like that ?
What the hell happened ?
How 's it going , Sergeant ?
I 'm his uncle ! Let go of me !
Rotten bastard .
Couldn 't he use GPS ? Why do I have to take him ?
Ain 't that it ?
Get the wire cutters .
Pull it back .
What 's that stink ?
So . Cho was killed here .
What the fuck is all this ?
So he invited Cho over , killed him ,
put the body in a sack , dragged it to his house , and then killed his wife ?
Crime of passion .
Make sure you photograph everything .
Here , there , that stuff over there .
Jong-gu !
Get over here !
Sergeant , come over here .
Shit !
Oh god ...
That cocksucker .
What kind of twisted freak is he ?
THE WAILING ( GOKSUNG )
Is that scary , or what ?
Scary , my ass .
Anyway , the whole town 's talking about it .
Who told you that story ?
Byeong-gyu .
That goddamned bastard ...
Now he 's spreading those stories to you , too ?
Well , from what I hear ,
there 's definitely something off with that guy .
Like what ?
The corner store owner went crazy ,
The guy at the mill dropped dead ,
and then Heung-gu turns up dead two days ago .
So ?
All this happened after that Japanese man arrived .
Quit talking out of your ass , you ignorant dope .
Who 're you calling ignorant ?
Look , the test results on Heung-guk came back today .
Apparently , he ate some fucked-up mushrooms .
What ?
You know . The ones with the drugs that make you go crazy .
His blood was full of that shit .
And there were tons of dried mushrooms at his place .
You really believe that ?
It 's what the results said !
Didn 't you ever try those mushrooms as a kid ?
Hell no .
All I know is , mushrooms don 't do that to you .
You saw that poor guy .
Mushrooms would never make you that way .
But I 'm right about the Japanese guy .
If everyone 's talking about him ,
there 's likely a good reason .
What the hell ?
Power 's gone out again .
Fuck .
I keep telling the Captain to get that damn wiring fixed .
Never listens !
What the fuck !
- What 's wrong ? - What the Christ was that ?
- That thing outside . - What 's outside ?
- Outside , that ... fuck ! - What 's your problem ?
What is it , man ?
You check it out .
- Me ? - Yes , you ! Dammit .
You want me to go out ?
I 'm telling you , asshole , to get your ass out there !
For crying out loud ...
Okay , I 'll go .
Come on , hurry !
Shit .
Who the fuck are you ? What the hell ?
Stop , goddamn it !
Stop it , you dirty slut ! You whore !
Eat this , too .
Damn , you 're heavy .
I 'm getting too old for this .
Don 't be ridiculous .
Old ladies tell me men can still get it up after 70 .
Then buy me some herbal supplements .
I keep having fucked-up nightmares .
What 're you doing in there ?
Oh hell . Shit !
Nothing ! Get away from the car .
- Don 't open it ! - What are you doing ?
For crying out loud !
Dad !
Dad ?
Look .
How do I look ?
Pretty .
Freakishly pretty .
How long were you watching ?
How much did you see ?
Don 't worry , I won 't tell .
So you saw everything .
No big deal . It 's not the first time .
What ?
Here .
It 's okay . Have a sip .
Hurry up !
Son of a bitch !
What took you so long ? Ignoring my calls ?
My mother-in-law got sick .
Now you 're using your mother-in-law as an excuse ?
You were taking a nap , I can tell !
No , I wasn 't . I swear .
Get to work .
Excuse me , ma 'am ?
What the hell ?
What are you doing ? Stop her .
Yes , sir .
Come with me , ma 'am .
Get off me !
Sergeant , get her out of here .
Back off , people .
What 's wrong with her ?
Please , calm down .
That idiot ...
Calm down , ma 'am .
Jong-gu .
Get cleaned up , man .
Hey , don 't beat yourself up .
It 's not your fault
that you 're a little girly-man with balls the size of peas .
Oh jeez .
Hello !
- Hey . - Hi , Hyo-jin .
Hello , Captain .
- How are you ? - Good .
- You 've got clean clothes for Daddy ? - Yeah .
Mom got you clean boxers and an undershirt .
Thanks , darling .
Take a shower .
I will . Go home .
You didn 't even eat , did you ?
All right , get out of here . Can 't you see Daddy 's working ?
See you .
Goodbye , officers .
- Bye . - See ya .
- Take care , sweetie . - Oh , my .
That scatterbrain .
Seong-bok ?
Yeah .
It just hit me .
What ?
That woman ...
What woman ?
The one whose house burned down ...
I knew I 'd seen her before .
It 's that naked woman from last night .
What ?
The woman who was standing here last night .
Crazy fools .
They didn 't burn to death . They were stabbed .
All three of them ?
Yeah .
Freaked the hell out of me , too .
Prime suspect is the missus who hung herself .
What the heck happened ?
Beats me .
Over here .
In here .
What ?
Give us a hand .
A little more .
Found it .
Idiot ! Don 't touch it with your bare hands !
What the ... ?
Are you a moron ?
That 's evidence .
He should 've wrapped it in cloth or something , right ?
Gokseong Police Station
So , she killed everyone ?
That 's what they said .
I 'll be damned .
So , that 's what happened .
Why did you call me ? Things are crazy at work .
Because of this case .
Remember what I told you before ?
What ?
How the Jap raped a woman ?
What about it ?
You filthy slut .
That woman .
It was her .
What the hell are you talking about ?
That woman he raped -
it 's the same woman whose house burned down .
She went crazy after that ,
and used to run around naked at night .
My wife saw her at the public bathhouse .
She was totally covered in rashes and boils ,
Mumbling gibberish the whole time .
Are you out of your mind ?
Byeong-gyu 's got to stop this .
Talking crap to his dimwitted buddies .
You worthless bastard . It was your theory .
I was just messing with you .
Who in their right mind would believe crap like that ?
No , I think you 're right .
It can 't be the mushrooms . That doesn 't make sense .
Gimme a break .
What are you looking at ?
Get outta here !
What ?
Ignore her . She 's been doing that all morning .
What a nut job .
So , how about you check with the local dermatologist .
See if there 's any medical records on Heung-guk or that woman .
Stop it , you tramp !
I can 't believe this .
It 's important , you idiot !
The rash is the link here .
Come on , hurry .
Stop it ! You could hurt somebody !
Community Health Center
Oh , my .
You 're really getting on my nerves !
Where do you live ?
Are you from this village ?
Hey .
Don 't come near me !
Dammit !
The lady killed them all .
What ?
In there . In that room .
What are you talking about ?
The old woman got a shaman to do some ritual ,
but the lady refused .
That 's why they all got killed .
Are you a family member ?
No , I 'm not .
Then who are you ?
Come with me .
Hey !
What the ... ?
You can 't go in there .
It 's all right .
Hey ...
Come on .
She killed them here .
The old woman got it the worst of it .
Her head was smashed open like a watermelon .
You saw with your own eyes ?
Of course I did .
How ?
The old woman tells me
the Jap is a ghost .
He was gonna suck her blood dry .
The Jap ?
Yeah .
The Jap with the limp .
Oh , him !
You 've seen him ?
Yeah .
How many times ?
Once or twice .
Be careful .
Why ?
The old woman says , if you keep seeing him around ,
it 's because he 's stalking you .
To suck your blood dry .
Wait here for a second .
Okay .
Get your ass over here .
What ?
Get over here now !
But I just found the dermatologist .
I found a witness .
So , get over here as fast as you can .
What the ... ?
Where 'd she go ?
What terrible sin did you commit , to be yelling like that ?
Are you feeling sick ?
Keep having weird dreams .
Who 's the medicine for ?
Hyo-jin 's not feeling well . She couldn 't go to school .
She 's burning up .
And where were you while she was so sick ?
I was getting her medicine .
What 's with you ? Take her to the hospital .
What on earth was that ?
Turn off the hose first .
Moron ...
Just coming into work now , are you ?
Hyo-jin wasn 't feeling well .
So now you 're blaming your daughter ?
I 'm not making it up .
Did you find your witness ?
No , sir .
After turning the whole town upside down .
You think this case is going to be your big break ?
Seong-bok 's been calling around .
That 's your excuse ?
Look at him . He can 't even wash the car .
Driving me up the wall .
Even the Chief heard about your witness .
Whether you lied , or let her get away -
you 're screwed .
Yes , sir .
This is driving me up the wall .
Don 't pay any attention to the crazy girl 's talk .
Not her . I 'm talking about this .
Family Tragedy Linked To Wild Mushrooms
" Murdered by ... wild mushrooms " ?
What did the dermatologist say ? Mushrooms ?
He wasn 't sure , so he referred Heung-guk to the hospital .
Told you . It can 't be the mushrooms .
It 's not impossible .
Shut your hole .
You know that story Byeong-gyu told you ?
There are so many .
The one about the naked man eating the deer carcass .
What 's gotten into you ?
At a crazy time like this ?
It 's because things are so crazy .
You know the guy who saw it , right ?
" Herbs Tonics "
Over here .
You may not believe it ,
but I saw it with my own eyes .
Look at this .
Can you see it ?
Sure .
I got 22 stitches .
From falling on your head while you were drunk ?
What are you talking about ?
I 'm too old to make shit up .
You got proof ?
Proof ?
Hell yes , proof !
I 'm not the kind to talk shit without backing it up .
Come look at this .
You ready ?
Look .
You see ?
Empty , right ?
I stayed the hell away from the mountains since that day .
Even put the store up for sale .
How is that proof ?
What ?
Damn you ...
That 's not the point .
The point is , when I opened my eyes ,
there he was - stark naked except for a diaper .
A diaper ?
That 's right .
A grown man ?
I 'm telling you .
- Grown men can wear diapers . - Get outta here .
Bladder control problems are surprisingly common in adults .
But why go into the woods to treat incontinence ?
- Incontinence ... - Am I talking to myself here ?
Anyway ,
he had his face buried in the carcass ,
his body covered in blood ...
his eyes all bloodshot .
Then he looked up ,
and all of a sudden ...
I haven 't slept since that day .
- He was chewing on the guts ? - That 's right .
- You saw him eating raw flesh ? - Yeah ...
Wait , look here .
See where the skin 's broken ?
Bastard even bit me .
Where does the guy live ?
Why , you gonna go there ?
I think I should .
Don 't . You 'll regret it .
It 's just a suspicion , but ...
You know how the villagers have been dying out recently ?
He 's got something to do with it .
He 's not human .
Give me his address .
It 's out in the middle of nowhere .
You 've gotta have a general idea .
It 's hard to explain in words .
It 's deep in the valley somewhere .
How much further is it ?
Still a ways ahead .
Shit !
What 's the matter ?
It 's there .
Over there .
I don 't see a house .
Look .
Right over there .
Whoa , isn 't that a deer ?
So , you weren 't making this up .
What did I tell you , dammit ?
What in God 's name ...
What 's happening ?
Look .
You know ...
What 's going on ?
That should do it , right ?
What ? You gotta show us the house .
It 's just over that hill .
It 's just the one house .
You can 't miss it .
You came all the way here . You should see it through .
Don 't touch me , I gotta go !
Where do you think you 're going ?
I said let go !
Shit ...
Hey !
Mister .
Mister ?
You all right ?
You fucking bastards .
We 're sorry .
Fuck off .
I 'm gonna get your asses sacked . You just wait .
We 're real sorry , okay ?
Fuck you .
You deserve to get scorched by lightning .
Where are you going ?
You got hit by lightning .
Hey !
What 's the point of taking
all those health tonics -
if it 's lightning that Kills you ?
How can something like this happen ?
What are the chances ?
But they 'll say , thanks to all those tonics ,
he survived .
Nurse ! Nurse !
It 's Park Heung-guk in 302 !
You gotta come now . It 's Park Heung-guk !
It 's an emergency !
Doctor !
What 's going on ?
Can anybody make sense
of what 's happening here ?
Let 's go back to the Jap 's house tomorrow .
There 's definitely something going on there .
Hyo-jin ?
Hyo-jin .
Baby !
Daddy 's right here .
Daddy 's right here , sweetie .
Look at Daddy .
Hyo-jin !
Look at me .
Look at Daddy .
Daddy 's here .
Dad ...
- I 'm right here . - Do something , Daddy !
What , sweetie ?
Someone keeps banging on the door ,
trying to get in .
Who ?
A strange man . He 's trying to get in .
It 's okay , it 's okay ...
Hyo-jin .
Hyo-jin ?
What is this ?
You 're all right ?
Morning , Dad .
But she never eats fish ...
Something 's wrong with her .
I heard you and Hyo-jin last night .
I asked the old lady next door to recommend a good shaman .
I 'm gonna consult with him , just so you know .
Got that ?
Okay .
Good .
Hey .
Say hello .
This is my nephew .
What , a priest ?
Not yet , he 's in training . A deacon .
We 'll need a translator to talk to the man .
You speak Japanese ?
Just a little .
He lived in Japan when he was young .
What 's that on your neck ?
Nothing .
You 've gotta be kidding me .
What 's your name , son ?
Yang E-sam . ( Two-three )
Is that your real name ?
Yes , sir .
Let 's go .
Get in .
Anybody home ?
What is it ?
Goddamn perv .
Look at this . What does it say ?
Uncle , this is illegal .
I know .
Then why ... We should stop .
If you won 't help , wait outside .
But Uncle !
Okay , you wait outside .
What are you staring at ?
Go keep a lookout .
What the fuck ?
- Son of a bitch ! - Get over here !
Get him off me !
What were you doing poking around the doghouse ?
Block the door !
Get over here !
Shit !
Seong-bok , you bastard !
Fucking bastard !
Where is it ?
Where did it go ?
Over there .
Seong-bok .
I think it 's the owner .
Seong-bok ?
Excuse me .
Are you all right ?
Yeah .
What 's the matter with you ?
Did you get bit ?
Huh ?
Say something , dammit .
He 's the criminal .
You 're scaring me , man .
Snap out of it .
It wasn 't just one or two people .
He took pictures of them when they were alive -
and then went back for more when they went crazy and died .
What the hell are you going on about ?
He 's the criminal .
That 's enough . I 'll deal with you later .
I 'm sure of it .
He ...
He took his victims ' belongings
and did something with them .
What did you see ?
Tell me !
Jeon Hyo-jin
You 're getting all wet !
Where is Hyo-jin ?
In the living room .
Hyo-jin .
You 're home early .
Did you lose your trainer ?
No , why ?
What 's this , then ?
It 's not mine .
Isn 't this your handwriting ?
I said , it 's not mine .
You know anything about a Japanese man living in the village ?
You 're dripping water all over the place .
Answer me . Do you know him or not ?
Did you meet him ?
Answer me .
You 're scaring her .
Get out for a sec .
Come on , this is serious . It 's you and me .
Daddy is a policeman . I 'll know if you lie .
Did you meet this man ?
Tell me .
Tell you what ?
Everything .
Where you met , what you did .
Why should I tell you ?
Because it 's important .
What 's so important ?
Answer me , girl !
I said , what 's so important ?
What 's so damn important ?
What the hell
is so damned important ?
You don 't even know what 's important .
Stop grilling me , goddamn it !
Fuck !
What are you doing ?
I thought you were sleeping .
What the hell ?
Yanking up your daughter 's skirt in the middle of the night ?
Speak , will you ?
Tell me , asshole !
Tell me , you fucking shithead !
Fuck you !
Stop staring , motherfucker !
Don 't call your daddy that !
Don 't you look at me !
Stop it ! Daddy said he was sorry .
I 'm gonna kill all of you .
How could you ?
I met the shaman today .
He thinks there 's a spirit in the house .
Something 's possessed Hyo-jin .
And if we don 't act , there 'll be dead bodies .
He 's supposed to be the best .
Why didn 't you answer my calls ?
Come with me , and don 't give me any crap .
Ask him where he stashed the stuff from in there .
The things in there ... where are they now ?
What things ?
He asks what things .
The stuff we saw before .
Things we saw ... before .
The photographs ?
You mean the pictures ?
Yeah , the pictures . And the other stuff .
Yes .
I burned them .
Sorry ?
He burned them .
Where ?
In the kitchen .
Bastard !
You !
What did you come here to do ?
Ask him again .
To travel .
To travel , he says .
Tell him I 'll throw him in jail if he doesn 't fess up .
Tell us the truth .
Even if I told you ,
you wouldn 't believe me .
He says you wouldn 't believe him .
Look , you translate everything I say ,
- word for word . - Yes , sir .
You fucking prick !
Oh ...
You loose-assed , dog-fucking son of a whore !
So , uh ...
What kind of tourist hangs pictures of dead people on his wall ?
Travel ... the dead ...
Why was this in your house ?
How did this ... ?
Who the fuck are you ?
Who are you ?
I know what you 're doing in this village .
I saw that room .
And I know what the fuck you 're doing to my daughter !
I want you ...
to stop what you 're doing , and leave this village quietly .
I mean it .
Leave .
Quietly .
This is Gokseong . My turf .
Don 't mess around
and get yourself killed . Just leave .
If you don 't leave , you 'll die .
If you heard me , say something . Or at least nod your fucking head !
Please answer .
So , you 're ...
Shut up , bitch !
You 're blowing me off ?
Oh , I 'm just not worth answering .
Is that it ?
You 're not even gonna listen , right ?
Ain 't that right ?
I 'm trying to speak to you ,
but you 're not listening !
What 's this ?
What the fuck is this ?
What the hell is all this ?
What the ...
What the fuck are these rituals you 're doing ? !
What the fuck are you doing in my town !
Do you know whose daughter you 're messing with ?
Son of a bitch !
Look out !
Jong-gu ?
Now what ?
Starting to see the light ?
I 'll give you three days .
Get out , or you 'll end up like your goddamned dog .
Translate .
Translate what I said .
How long has it been like this ?
Just a few days .
So ?
The symptoms -
they 're the same as the others ' .
There 's gotta be an explanation for what she has .
They say they don 't know .
What is it ?
Oh God !
Who the fuck did this ?
What ? !
You okay ?
Get your husband .
Who did this ?
Who the fuck did this ?
Jong-gu !
What 's the matter !
Does he drink a lot ?
It 's nothing to worry about .
I 'll take the needles out in 20 minutes .
Cut back on the drinking .
Yeah .
It 's started . You better brace yourself .
What I said the other day-we 'll do it tomorrow .
Where is Hyo-jin ?
You can 't back out now . Get the money for the ritual .
Where is she ?
At home . Where else would she be ?
I asked the old lady next door to watch her .
You left her alone with a stranger ?
Are you out of your minds ?
Don 't move .
Hyo-jin .
Baby .
- What 's the matter ? - Oh my God !
Hyo-jin !
Drop that , baby .
Don 't cry . It 's okay .
It 's okay .
It 'll be okay .
Quick ! Call 911 !
This is all the work of that Jap .
Ever since we went to his house ,
my body 's been in pain .
I 'm burning up . I 'm seeing things .
A man 's face comes out of the wall .
I don 't think he 's alive .
We 've gotta do something ,
or that bastard will get us first .
Shut the damn door !
What 's in that jar ?
Which one ?
The one with the red lid .
It 's just soy sauce .
Bring it over .
What , are you deaf ?
Out of the way , come on .
Stand back .
What is that ?
I 'll be fucked ...
It 's a real wicked spirit we 've got here .
You don 't want to leave , do you ?
Let 's go !
Stop it !
Hyo-jin !
Come here , you !
You met up with something recently
you weren 't supposed to ?
I don 't follow you .
Did you disturb someone ?
Of all the evil I 've seen , this is the strongest .
You disturbed it .
Oh , God ! What do we do now ?
Who is it ?
Who did you disturb ?
Tell him .
A Japanese man ...
I Knew it .
That 's no man .
That 's a ghost .
All the things happening around here are his doing .
If nothing is done , it 's not just your daughter ,
but everything that walks on two feet will perish .
Sir !
This is Park Chun-bae . He owns this house .
He killed his wife , too ?
It appears so .
What 's that bastard 's name ?
Park Chun-bae .
Then what ?
What do you mean , what ? Gotta get rid of it .
Either banish it , or kill it .
I 'm casting a deadly hex tomorrow at the hour of the dog .
Yes , sir .
You got the money ?
How much ?
About 10 grand , don 't you think ?
I 'll have it ready .
Good .
Listen .
What I 'm doing tomorrow -
it 's no ordinary ritual .
I 'll be casting a death hex .
It 's incredibly dangerous .
So you can 't do anything that would taint it .
No intercourse . Watch what you eat and drink .
Or the spell will backfire .
Yes , sir .
Okay then . You can go .
Can I ask you something ?
What ?
That Japanese guy .
You said he 's a ghost .
So ?
I don 't get how a living person can be a ghost .
It 's not a living human .
He died a long time ago .
He must have been human once .
But not anymore .
So then ,
the ghost got inside him ?
Well , that 's how it started .
Not everything that moves , breathes , and talks is alive .
Countless people have perished because they didn 't understand that .
If it 's not stopped ...
that demon will destroy this village .
Demon ?
An evil ghost !
Even among other demons , he 's a master of evil .
If that 's true ,
why did it have to be
your daughter ?
What sin did that young girl ever commit ?
Yes .
If you go fishing , do you know what you 'll catch ?
No .
He 's just fishing .
Not even he knows what he 'll catch .
He just threw out the bait , and your daughter took it .
That 's all it was .
Park Chun-bae
- This one ? - No .
Money . Yes , money .
21 dollars more .
- No ! - That 's okay .
Oh , come on .
Tell him to stop .
Stop !
I said stop !
Jong-gu !
What 's the matter ?
Look at me .
Baby ?
Hyo-jin !
Please make him stop ...
Please ...
Please make him stop .
Dad !
Dad ...
Hyo-jin .
We shouldn 't do this ...
Stop , you bastards !
Stop !
Fucking bastards !
Stop right now .
Stop !
Stop .
I said stop !
I 'm gonna smash your heads in !
Stop , I said .
Get out .
Now !
Everything started on that day ?
I 'll try speaking to the Father .
What you 're telling me is true ?
Yes .
And you said the shaman told you this .
From their perspective ,
a ghost is the spirit of a dead man .
But that man is alive .
I 've heard about this man , too .
Rumor has it he 's a renowned professor .
And there are darker , more disturbing rumors -
Some say he 's a Buddhist monk .
But they 're just rumors . How can you believe them ?
No , Father . They 're definitely not rumors .
You sound terribly sure .
Did you see it with your own eyes ?
How can you be sure without seeing for yourself ?
Take her back to the hospital . Trust the doctor .
There 's nothing the Church can do for you now .
Come with me to the Jap 's .
Sorry ?
I gotta see for myself
if he 's really a ghost or not .
If he is ,
then I won 't be able to kill him .
Where is he ?
Is everyone here ?
Yeah .
Why 'd you call us so early ?
Cheol-yeong couldn 't come . His sow is farrowing .
What 's with your face ?
This ain 't a joke ?
You 're serious , right ?
Yeah .
Cross your heart , or your mom 's a whore ?
You prick !
This is no time for jokes .
What a fucking loser .
Go !
- Nothing ? - No .
Don 't just stand around . Check the back .
What 's that ?
Fucking bastard ...
Byeong-gyu ! Over here .
Hurry up .
Is that him ?
Over there .
Where ? Follow me .
Where ?
What the ... ?
Who 's that ?
What is that thing ?
Don 't come any closer .
Back off .
Stop it .
That 's enough , man !
Sorry , man . You all right ?
Stop it !
What are you doing to him ?
He 's not ... right ...
Put it down .
- Let go ! - We can talk this out .
E-sam !
Dad ...
Look .
There 's another one !
That 's him .
That 's him !
Get him !
Where ?
Son of a bitch !
There he is .
Over there .
Son of a bitch !
Where is he ?
Over there .
Where ?
What 's wrong ?
- Come over here . - What ? Why did you stop ?
What 's the matter ?
Come over here !
Jong-gu .
Where 'd he go ?
Where is that bastard ?
Hey , man !
Get down here .
Do you see him ?
Hey !
Where did he go ?
Jong-gu !
I gotta catch him .
Gotta catch that bastard .
Catch that bastard .
I can 't believe this ...
- Gotta save my baby . - Come on .
Let 's go down .
I gotta save my little girl .
- We 'll get him . - I 've gotta find him , and save my baby .
- Don 't worry , we will . - Okay ?
Get your act together , man .
We gotta save her .
I know , man .
I know .
I have to save my daughter ...
Come on , man .
I have to catch that bastard .
Don 't cry , man .
Dammit , Jong-gu !
Wife Please , pick up .
Shit ! Was that a person ?
Wife
The rat fell into the trap .
You all right , baby ?
You okay ?
I 'm okay .
Come here .
You 're okay now ?
Drink up .
Good girl .
Leave it .
I want to tidy up a little .
Leave it . We 've got the shaman to thank for everything .
Get some rest . You must be exhausted .
Shaman
Damn fool .
Suspect arrested in the mushroom-tonic case ...
Victims have developed severe mental derangement ...
Mr. Yang E-sam ?
Yes .
The landlady was a victim .
Your uncle must 've taken the tonic , too .
It 's turned the town upside down .
We 've gotta bring him in .
You should get a lawyer .
After all ,
he 's a victim , too .
What the fuck ?
What are you doing here ?
Get out .
Missed calls - Shaman
What the hell ?
What the ... ?
Hello .
It 's me .
Where are you ?
What about you ?
Don 't ask me anything .
You need to get to your daughter . Now .
Tell me what 's going on ?
I 'm at your place .
Get back to your house , now .
First tell me what 's going on .
I misread the divination .
It 's not him .
What are you talking about ?
I cast the hex on the wrong ghost .
I saw a woman in front of your house .
I made a grave mistake .
A terrible , terrible mistake .
It 's not the Japanese man .
That woman is the evil spirit .
It was all her doing .
So , go home now .
I 'm on my way there , too .
Then ...
Who 's the Japanese man ?
He was trying to kill that woman
in order to save people from her .
Understand ?
That Japanese man -
he 's a shaman , like me .
Was the woman ...
wearing white ?
Did you see her ?
A young woman ?
That 's her .
... defend us in battle .
Be our safeguard against the wickedness
and snares of the devil .
Where is she ?
Where 's Hyo-jin ? !
Hyo-jin !
What is it ?
Where are you headed in the dark of night ?
I 'm asking you .
Where is my daughter ?
Where is she ?
Girl about this tall ?
Yeah .
Hyo-jin ?
That 's right .
She 's possessed by an evil spirit .
The old woman tells me the Jap is a ghost .
He 's trying to suck her blood dry ...
Shut the fuck up !
Answer me , bitch !
Where is Hyo-jin ?
- Have you seen the Jap ? - Where 's my daughter ?
At your home , where else ?
She 's not home .
She is .
She just got back .
Don 't go now -
or you 'll all die .
If you go now , your whole family will perish .
What are you talking about ?
The Jap is waiting for you ...
to annihilate your family .
He 's dead .
He 's not dead .
Death cannot touch him .
The demon will soon enter your home .
You 've seen the demon ?
At the house of the hanged woman .
It was a dream .
It was no dream .
I laid a trap for it .
Wait here , until he 's caught .
That 's all you need to do .
What are you ?
A woman or a ghost ?
Why do you ask ?
I need to know ...
If I can put my faith in you .
Just believe ,
and your family will be saved .
What are you ?
Someone trying to save your daughter .
A woman .
I called all her friends ...
Hyo-jin ?
Hyo-jin !
Baby .
When will the demon come ?
It 's already there .
Hyo-jin .
It 's already there ?
Let me ask you one thing .
What is your true form ?
What do you think is my true form ?
The devil .
You 're the devil .
Why can 't you answer ?
You 've already said it .
I 'm the devil .
Shaman
I 'm almost there .
Where are you ? Are you home ?
I 'm with the woman now .
You mustn 't let her tempt you .
Never .
Whatever she tells you ,
you must go to your daughter now .
Do you understand me ?
Understand ?
Do you ?
Is that your shaman ?
Don 't believe what he tells you .
They 're in on it together .
Isn 't that right ?
You 're already certain I 'm the devil .
That 's why you came here ...
carrying that sickle .
My words , whatever I say -
they won 't change your mind .
No .
That 's not true .
There 's no doubt .
You came here to confirm your suspicions about me .
That 's not true !
If you say
you 're not the devil ,
and reveal your true form to me -
I 'll leave you alone .
When the demon is snared ,
the rooster will cry three times .
Wait until the third cry .
You 'll leave me alone ?
Yes .
Two more .
Do not waver .
You 'll leave ?
Yes .
I 'll leave you alone .
Who said I 'd let you leave ?
Then let me ask you one thing .
What ?
Why in God 's name is he doing this ?
Because her father has sinned .
What sin ?
What sin did I commit ?
Her father suspected another .
He tried to kill him , and finally succeeded .
But my daughter ... !
My daughter ...
My daughter got sick first !
How can that ...
How can that possibly ...
One more , now .
How can that be ... ?
Don 't do it .
What are you saying ?
Whether you walk out of here or not is completely up to you .
Touch me and see .
A ghost does not have flesh and bones ,
and you see I have both .
Park Chun-bae
No .
That 's not it .
It 's you .
No .
This is all your doing .
Don 't do it .
Hyo-jin ...
No !
What are you doing ?
Don 't !
Why are you troubled ?
Hyo-jin .
Honey ...
Mother ...
Look at me .
Look at me !
Please .
Look at me .
Please ...
Please !
Hyo-jin !
Hyo-jin ...
Hyo-jin .
Hyo-jin !
Why is there doubt in your heart ?
See my hands , and my feet .
You can see it is I.
Myself .
Oh Lord ...
Hyo-jin ...
It 's okay .
My baby .
You know Daddy 's a policeman .
I 'll take care of everything .
Daddy will .